# KIREE BELLAMY

# Junior Fullstack Developer



+46 (0)73 417 2218



in www.linkedin.com/in/kireebellamy



kireebellamy@gmail.com



https://github.com/Swewi



Stockholm



https://tinyurl.com/KireesCV

# About Me

I am a Junior Software Developer with a Diploma in Fullstack Software Development from Code Institute. Proficient in HTML, CSS, Javascript, Python, and Django, but with much to learn!

I have 10+ years of experience in Customer Service and hospitality. I am a valuable team player with strong communication and problem-solving skills. I am keen to start working in the tech industry as a member of a development team where I can grow and contribute!

#### **KEY SKILLS**

Languages: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Python

Databases: MySQL, and postgres

Frameworks: Flask, Django, and Bootstrap Version Control: Heroku, GitHub, and Git

#### **COLLABORATION PROJECTS**

- Code Institute Hackathon July 2024 Proud Coders: 3rd place - Chronicles of Pride.
- Code Institute Hackathon August 2024 Pixel Pioneers: Participant - Invasion 83

# **EDUCATION**

# **Code Institute**

Diploma in Fullstack Development Februrary 2024 - July 2024

### **University of Auckland**

Bachelor of Science 1994 - 1999

### PORTFOLIO PROJECTS

- Portfolio Project 5: Mildew detection in <u>cherry leaves</u> - A small streamlit and machine learning project to visualise powdery mildew on cherry leaves. I used Python and Streamlit for this project.
- Portfolio Project 4: Werecat Blog A blog site for a pair of crafty women. I used HTML, CSS vanilla and Bootstrap, JavaScript, Python, Postgres, and Django for this project.
- Portfolio Project 3: Wings Text-Based Game - A good old-fashioned 'pick a path' textbased game. I used Python for this project.
- Portfolio Project 2: Testing your STP knowledge - A short quiz game to test your Terry Pratchett knowledge. I used JavaScript, HTML, and CSS for this project.
- Portfolio Project 1: NZ Wars a brief overview - A very brief overview of the New Zealand Wars. I used HTML, and CSS for this project.

# KIREE BELLAMY

# Junior Fullstack Developer

+46 (0)73 417 2218



in www.linkedin.com/in/kireebellamy



kireebellamy@gmail.com



https://github.com/Swewi



Stockholm



https://tinyurl.com/KireesCV

### WORK EXPERIENCE

### Personal Development

2022 - present

- Code Institute Course
- Course and job related research.

Business Startup - Sweet As!

2021 - 2022

#### Stockholm - Sweden

(Old Fashioned Candy Shop)

- Writing and adapting business plans, to meet the changing economic environment.
- Writing and adapting budgets to meet the changing economic environment.
- Voluntarily suspending the start-up process due to massive upheaval in the economic climate.

# Skafferiet I Ekoparken Stockholm - Sweden

2017 - 2020

(Shift Supervisor)

- Interact with customers and colleagues from around the world.
- Inform customers about available products, and any specials, take and deliver orders.
- · Ability to switch between front and back of house multiple times per shift as required.

#### **Career Break**

2013 - 2017

• Moving country and settling in.

# Mountain Warehouse

2013 - 2015

#### Portsmouth - Great Britain

(Retail Assistant)

- Maximising sales by using my personal experience of the brand and products.
- Building relationships with customers and colleagues to benefit customer experience.

### **SOFT SKILLS**

- Communication
- Compassion
- Creative Problem-solving
- Curiosity
- Persistence
- Resilience

# LANGUAGE

- English Native
- Swedish Basic

# SHORT COURSES AND CERTIFICATES

- June 2024 Le Wagon: Intro to SQL
- June 2024 W3 Schools: Learn Accessibility
- December 2023 Code Institute: 5 Day Coding Challenge

#### **MEMBERSHIPS**

 Tjejer Kodar - One of Sweden's largest female-oriented coding organisations

# ADDITIONAL INFORMATION AND INTERESTS

- I am working on designing a website for my partner and I to use as a showcase and sales platform.
- · I am designing a website my partner can use to track and see trends in their blood sugar
- I enjoy gaming, I play minecraft primarily, however I do not limit myself to only PC gaming, I love playing on our switch, or one of several consoles we have in the house.
- I make and sell handcrafts, I work with paracord and rope making leashes, collars, braclets, keyrings, and weird bits and pieces. I make chainmaile bradelets and earings, and I use yarn, both natural and man-made, to nålbind.